androidshock.com 2015-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Android Shock

At AndroidShock, we are keenly aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we let you know what information we collect when you surf our site, why we collect it, and how we use it to improve your experience. Our Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information.

### The information we collect and store

_Information you provide._  When you register an account, we collect some personal information, such as your name, phone number, email address and home and business postal addresses. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

_Cookies._  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

_IP address._  Every computer and device connected to the Internet is assigned a unique number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. Since these numbers are usually assigned in country-based blocks, an IP address can often be used to identify the country, state, and city from which a computer is connecting to the Internet. Because IP addresses need to be used by websites in order for the Internet to function, website owners have access to the IP addresses for their visitors regardless of whether or not they visit AndroidShock. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. AndroidShock does not share actual IP address information with AndroidShock customers.

### How we use personal information

_Personal Information._ In the course of using the Service, we may collect personal information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, and (v) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of those communications, or update your account settings information.

### Google AdSense

We use Google AdSense as a third-party advertisement vendor. To learn more about privacy policy of Google, [click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics as a third-party analytics platform.  To learn more about privacy policy of Google, [click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Information security

The security of your information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [privacy@zorilla.biz](mailto:privacy@zorilla.biz).

### Outbound links

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

_This policy was last modified on 10/10/2012_
